shoplouun.com 2016-05-12

# louun — Privacy

Privacy Policy  
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and  
selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as  
your name, address and email address.  
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s  
internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that  
helps us learn about your browser and operating system.  
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you  
emails about our store, new products and other updates.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT

How do you get my consent?  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction,  
verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a  
purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for  
that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like  
marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or  
provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdrawing your consent  
for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of  
your information, at anytime, by contacting us at louunjewelry@gmail.com or  
mailing us at:  
louun  
515 S. Harvard Blvd. #303 Los Angeles, CA 90020

SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do  
so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online  
e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to  
you.  
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the  
general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind  
a firewall.

Payment:  
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then  
Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment  
Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction  
data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase  
transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information  
is deleted.  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as  
managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of  
brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card  
information by our store and its service providers.  
For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service here  
or Privacy Statement here.

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and  
disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform  
the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways  
and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies  
in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your  
purchase-related transactions.  
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so  
you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be  
handled by these providers.  
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have  
facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us.  
So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of  
a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to  
the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its  
facilities are located.  
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is  
processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your  
personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to  
disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party  
website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy  
or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links  
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our  
site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and  
encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and  
follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost,  
misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is  
encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a  
AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet  
or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements  
and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

SECTION 7 - COOKIES

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that  
you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information  
about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last  
visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the  
number of visits  
_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of  
the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the  
contents of your cart.  
_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password,  
this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of  
majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of  
majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your  
consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please  
review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect  
immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes  
to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that  
you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what  
circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information  
may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell  
products to you.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal  
information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more  
information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at  
louunjewelry@gmail.comor by mail at  
louun  
[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]  
515 S. Harvard Blvd. #303 Los Angeles, CA 90020
